风暴即将来临
Storm's coming.
而你们和你们的父亲 你们正要被卷入这风暴
And you boys and your daddy, you are smack in the middle of it.
(忆往昔)
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快 迪恩 快跑
Take your brother outside as fast as you can. Now, Dean. Go!
爸爸想让我们继续他的工作
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things.The family business.
我们一生都在寻找这个恶魔
Our whole lives we been searching for this demon.
塞缪尔·柯尔特造了一把枪
Samuel Colt made a gun.
传说能杀死任何生物
They say this gun can kill anything.
我们最终知道那个恶魔的去处
We finally know where this demon's gonna be.
以及如何才能杀死它
And now, we know how to kill it.
越来越多的恶魔在向我们靠近
More and more demons are walking among us.
- 你不是我父亲 - 到底发生了什么事
- You're not my dad. - What's going on?
我觉得爸爸被附身了
I think he's possessed.
我的计划都是为了你们 萨姆
I have plans for you, Sammy.
你和象你一样有超能力的孩子
You and all the children like you.
它就在我的体内 我能感觉到 向我开枪
It's inside me. I can feel it.Hey, shoot me.
我撑不了多久
I can't hold on to it much longer.
- 你为什么不杀了它 - 我们现在还有柯尔特
- Why didn't you kill it? - We got the Colt.
我们还剩有一发子弹
We still have one bullet left.
(现在)
快滚开
Get back!
不然我就杀了你 我对天发誓
Or I'll kill you, I swear to God.
你不会的
You won't.
你得留着那子弹对付其他人
You're saving that bullet for someone else.
你想试试看吗
You wanna bet?
我的天那
Oh, my God.
- 爸爸… - 这都是我干的吗
- Dad? - Did I do this?
爸爸
Dad?
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
快 动作快点 乘客伤势严重 已经昏迷
Significant passenger space intrusion.Unresponsive.
血压 180/50
BP, 180 over 50. Heart rate
血压 180/15 心跳 95
BP, 100 over 50. Heart rate, 99, 95
- 告诉我他们还好吗 - 别乱动 你得躺下
- Tell me if they're okay. - You have to stay still.
他们还活着吗
Are they even alive?
萨姆
Sam?
爸爸
Dad?
有人吗
Anybody?
这里是拯救郡护士咨询处
Shiloh County, Nurses' Station.
要把您的电话转过去吗？
How can I transfer your call?
好的 我帮你转过去
Of course, I'll transfer your call.
请问…
Excuse me.
嗨
Hi.
我… 我记得我出了车祸
I think I was in a car accident...
还有我爸爸和弟弟 我得找到他们
with my dad and my brother.I just need to find them.
你有在听吗
Hello?
[邪恶力量 第2季第1集]
萨姆
Sammy.
你看上去还不错…
You look good...
细想起来
considering...
哦 不
Oh, no.
伙计 告诉我你能听到我说的话
Man, tell me you can hear me.
爸爸他怎么样
How's Dad?
他没事吧
Is he okay?
伙计 别这样一声不吭
Come on, you're the psychic.
你是有通灵能力的 你到是说句话呀
Give me some ghost whispering or something.
你父亲醒了
Your father's awake.
你随时可以进去见他
You can go see him, if you like.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
医生 那我哥哥怎么样了
Doc, what about my brother?
他的伤势很严重
He sustained serious injury.
大量失血 肝和肾也严重损伤
Blood loss, contusions to his liver and kidney.
不过我最担心的是他头上的撞伤
It's the head trauma I'm worried about.
已经有脑部水肿的迹象
There's early signs of cerebral edema.
好吧 那我们能做些什么
Well, what can we do?
只有他醒过来 我们才能确诊
We won't know his full condition until he wakes up.
如果
If...
- 他能醒过来的话 - 如果…
- ...he wakes up. - If?
- 我得实话实说… - 得了吧 医生 我正醒着呢
- To be honest... - I'm waking up.
普通人象他这样的伤势 能活到现在 已经是十分罕见了
most people with his injury wouldn't have survived this long.
他的意志很强
He's fighting very hard.
但是你必须面对现实 孩子
But you need to have realistic expectations, son.
别信他的 萨姆
Come on, Sam.Go find some Hoodoo priest...
去找个巫师来念点咒语什么的
to lay some mojo on me.
我就会好了
I'll be fine.
听到没 萨姆
Sam.
这个 你拿着
All right. Here.
给他们这是我的保险
Give them my insurance.
艾罗伊· 迈克罗卡迪
"Elroy McGillicuddy"?
以及他的两个心爱的儿子
And his two loving sons.
那…
So...
关于迪恩 医生还说了什么
What else did the doctor say about Dean?
没有了
Nothing.
听着… 如果医生帮不了他 我们必须帮他 无论如何
Look, if the doctors won't do anything, then we'll have to. That's all.
我不知道 但我会想办法…
I don't know. I'll find some...
也许去找个巫师来对他念点咒语什么的
Hoodoo priest and lay some mojo on him and...
我会去找人帮忙的
We'll look for someone.
没错
Yeah.
但是 萨姆…
But, Sam...
我不知道是不是能找到这样的人
I don't know if we'll find anyone.
为什么不能
Why not?
我曾找到过一个意念治疗者
I found that faith healer before.
但再找到这样的机会微乎其微
All right, that was one in a million.
那又如何 难道我们就坐着等待奇迹出现
What, then we just sit here with our thumbs up our ass?
我不是这个意思 我说了我们当然得去找
No, I said we'd look.
我会寻遍每一寸土地
I'll check under every stone.
柯尔特在哪里
Where's the Colt?
你的儿子正在死亡边缘 而你却还在担心柯尔特
Your son is dying, and you're worried about the Colt?
我们在追杀这个恶魔 但它也可能在追杀我们
We are hunting this demon and maybe it's hunting us too.
那把枪可能是我们唯一的筹码
That gun may be our only card.
在车里
It's in the trunk.
他们把车拖到I- 83公路一码外
They dragged the car to a yard off I-83.
好吧 你得在流浪汉发现车里的东西前 找到柯尔特
You gotta clean out that trunk before some junk man sees what's inside.
我已经叫鲍比来处理了 他已经出门一个多小时了
I already called Bobby.He's like an hour out.
他会把那车拖回他的住处
He's gonna tow the Impala back to his place.
那好 那你去见鲍比
All right. You go meet up with Bobby.
拿到柯尔特 带回来给我
You get that Colt and bring it back.
- 注意医院的安检 - 我明白了
- And you watch out for hospital security. - I think I got it covered.
嘿
Hey.
拿着这个
Here.
表上列出了我要的东西 让鲍比给我弄来
I made a list of things I need.Have Bobby pick them up.
阿拉伯树胶？艾布拉姆油？
Acacia? Oil of Abramelin?
你要这些东西干吗 - 自卫
- What's this stuff for? - Protection.
我说 爸爸…
Hey, Dad.
你也听见那个恶魔的话了
You know the demon?
他说他为我和像我一样的孩子 制定了一个计划
He said he had plans for me and children like me.
你知道那是什么计划吗
You have any idea what he meant by that?
不 我不清楚
No, I don't.
你肯定知道些什么
Well, you sure know something.
哦 上帝
Oh, man.
迪恩看到这肯定会气疯的
Dean is gonna be pissed.
听着 萨姆
Look, Sam, it's
这东西根本经不起拖了
This just aingt worth a tow.
要我说我们把车清空 其他部分当废品卖了
I say we empty the trunk and sell the rest for scrap.
不行
No.
迪恩会杀了我的 如果那样做
Dean would kill me if we did that.
一旦他好起来 他会想办法修好它的
When he gets better, he's gonna wanna fix this.
但是没有什么东西能修的了
There's nothing to fix.
车壳都变形了 引擎也损毁了
Frame's a pretzel. The engine's ruined.
基本没有值得修复的零件了
There's barely any parts worth salvaging.
听我说 鲍比
Listen to me, Bobby.
哪怕只有一个部分可以用 这就够了
If there's only one working part, that's enough.
我们不能就此放弃…
We're not just gonna give up on...
行
Okay.
照你的意思办
You got it.
这张单子…
Here.
爸爸想让你给他准备这些东西
Dad asked if you could get this stuff for him.
约翰要这些东西做什么
What John want with this?
保护大家免受那个恶魔的侵害
Protection from the demon.
怎么了
What?
- 没什么 只是… - 鲍比
- Oh, nothing. It's just - Bobby.
爸爸他到底要做什么
What's going on?
别这样 爸爸
Come on, Dad.
你得帮我
You gotta help me.
我得快点好起来 重回你们身边
I gotta get better.I gotta get back in there.
我是说 你根本没有做任何事来帮我
I mean, you haven't called a soul for help.
你甚至没有尝试过
You haven't even tried.
难道你不准备做任何事么
Aren't you gonna do anything?
难道你不打算说些什么吗
Aren't you even gonna say anything?
我做了一切你要我做的事
I've done everything you have ever asked me.
所有的一切
Everything.
我放弃了曾经所拥有的一切
I have given everything I've ever had.
而现在你就打算坐在那里看着我死去
Are you're just gonna sit there and you're gonna watch me die?
我真不知道怎么会有你这样的父亲
What the hell kind of father are you?
那是什么
What is that?
我想你应该看不见
I take it you didn't see that.
救命 救命 救命
Help. Help. Help.
嘿 这里有人需要帮助
Hey, I need some help in here!
我…
I can't...
不能呼吸了
breathe.
萨姆 快告诉我 你的能听到我的话
Sammy, tell me you can freaking hear me.
医院里有恶魔在游荡 你得想办法让我醒过来
There's something in the hospital.Bring me back. We gotta hunt this thing.
听到没 萨姆
Sam.
你怎么一直不说话
You're quiet.
- 你认为我是白痴吗 - 你在说什么
- Think I wouldn't find out? - What are you talking about?
那些你向鲍比要的东西 你不是用来提防恶魔的
That stuff Bobby. You don't use it to ward off a demon.
你是用来召唤恶魔的
You use it to summon one.
你正计划把那个恶魔召唤到这里
You plan on bringing the demon here.
傻瓜似的要跟它来个了结
Having some stupid, macho showdown.
- 我的确有个计划 萨姆 - 那正是我想说的
- I have a plan, Sam. - That's exactly my point.
迪恩奄奄一息 而你还在想计划
Dean is dying and you have a plan.
比起救你的亲生儿子
You care more about killing this demon...
- 你更关心如何杀死那个恶魔 - 伙计 别这样
than saving your own son.Don't do this.
不要过早下定论
Do not tell me how I feel.
- 我做这些是为了帮迪恩 - 怎么帮
- I'm doing this for Dean. - How?
报仇怎么能帮到他
How is revenge gonna help him?
除了你自己 你不关心其他任何人
You're not thinking about anybody but yourself.
- 你还是像以前一样的自私和顽固 - 够了 你们俩 别这样
- It's the same selfish obsession. - Don't do this.
真是可笑 我认为那也是你的执著所在
I thought this was your obsession too.
这个恶魔杀死了你的母亲和女友
This demon killed your mother. Killed your girlfriend.
是你恳求加入这场战斗的
You begged me to be part of this hunt.
如果上次你就杀了那个家伙的话
If you killed it when you had the chance
现在这一切都不会发生了
none of this would've happened.
那时候它附在你身上
It was possessing you.
如果我那么做了 你也会死的
I would've killed you too.
但你哥哥现在就不会躺在那里不省人事了
Your brother would be awake.
- 别再说了 你们两个 - 得了吧
- Shut up. Both of you. - Go to hell.
从一开始我就不该拉你进来
I should've never taken you along in the first place.
- 我就知道这是个错 - 我说了 "别再说了"
- It was a mistake. - I said shut up!
伙计 我成斯韦兹了
Dude, I full - on Swayze'd that mother.
这是什么？什么？
What the? What is?
有事要发生
Something's going on out there.
准备好了吗 准备好了
All clear. Clear.
- 仍然没有脉搏 - 不
- Still no pulse. - No.
- 还是没有脉搏 - 好吧 我们再来一次 360伏
- Still no pulse. - Okay, let's go again, 360.
充电 准备好了吗
Charging. All clear?
准备好了
Clear. Clear.
加油 加油
Come on. Come on.
还是没有脉搏
No pulse. Baseline, 36.
- 我们再来一次 - 准备就绪
- Ready. - Charged.
就绪
Clear. Standing by.
好吧 我们再来一次
Still nothing. No pulse. Okay, let's go again.
正在充电
Charging. All clear?
- 充电完成 - 该死的东西
- Clear. - You get the hell away from me.
别碰我的身体
Stay back.
没有反应 用心肺复苏
No change. Starting CPR.
我说了别碰我的身体
I said, get back!
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
- 3 2 1 - 还是没有脉搏
- Three, two, one. - Still nothing.
有脉搏了 脱离危险
We have a pulse. We're back into sinus rhythm.
不用担心 萨姆
Don't worry, Sammy.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
我要在那东西找上我前找到它
I'm getting that thing before it gets me.
那应该是个灵魂
It's some kind of spirit...
但我能抓到它
but I could grab it.
如果我能抓到它
And if I can grab it...
就能杀了它
I can kill it.
你们都看不见我吗
Can't you see me?
你们为什么都象看不见我一样
Why won't you look at me?
发生什么事了
Now what?
来个人和我说句话呀
Somebody talk to me.
随便说点什么 求你了
Say something, please.
你能看到我吗
Can you see me?
能看到
Yeah.
好了 冷静下来
Hi, just calm down.
- 你叫什么 - 泰萨
- What's your name? - Tessa.
很好泰萨 我叫迪恩
Okay, good, Tessa. I'm Dean.
到底发生了什么事
What's happening to me?
我…
Am I?
死了吗
Am I dead?
那得看情况了
That sort of depends.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我只是来做个阑尾切除手术
I just came in for an appendectomy.
我也不想听到坏消息 但是…
I hate to bear bad news...
我想你可能得了严重的并发症
but I think there were some complications.
可能这不过是个梦罢了
It's just a dream. That's all. This is just...
只不过是个奇怪
a very weird...
而又异常真实的梦
unbelievably vivid dream.
泰萨
Tessa...
这不是梦
it's not a dream.
那这又算怎么一回事
Then what else could it be?
你有没有听说过灵魂出窍
You ever heard of an out - of - body experience?
你是什么人 信仰灵魂者吗
What are you, some New Age - y guy?
你认为我是玩水晶球的巫师 还是听雅尼的音乐
You see me messing with crystals or listening to Yanni?
事实上 这是个古老的思想
It's actually a very old idea.
但有多种称谓
It's got a lot of different names. Bilocation...
幻影 鬼魂 幽灵
crisis apparitions, fetches.
我认为我们正处于这种状态
I think it's happening to us.
如果是这样…
And if it is...
就说明我们是濒死之人的…
it means that we're spirits...
灵魂
of people close to death.
这么说我们即将死去吗
So we're gonna die?
不会的
No.
如果我们坚持下去就不会
Not if we hold on.
我们的身体好起来
Our bodies can get better.
你可以马上回到 自己的身体里醒过来
You can snap back in there and wake up.
你说你感觉一些东西 那是什么意思
What do you mean, you "felt something"?
我是说 那感觉像…
I mean, it felt like
像是迪恩
Like Dean.
好像他就在这里 只不过我们看不见
Like he was there, just out of eyeshot or something.
我不知道是我神经质还是其他什么的
I don't know if it's my psychic thing or what.
那你觉得这有可能吗
But do you think it's even possible?
你觉得他的灵魂有可能在我们身边吗
You think his spirit could be around?
一切都有可能
Anything's possible.
好吧 有一个方法能够知道
Well, there's one way to find out.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
- 我去找些东西 很快就回来 - 等一下 萨姆
- I gotta pick something up. I'll be back. - Wait, Sam.
我保证 在迪恩好起来之前
I promise, I won't hunt this demon.
不去想杀死那个恶魔的事
Not until we know Dean's okay.
我不得不说 我很惊讶
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
- 惊讶什么 - 你
- With what? - You.
大多数人处在你这个位置 现在肯定惊恐不已了
Most people in your spot would be Jell-O by now...
但你似乎能坦然面对 甚至比我还坦然
but you're taking this pretty well. Maybe a little better than me.
不要误解我的意思
Don't get me wrong.
我起初也怕得要死
I was pretty freaked at first.
但现在我不知道 也许我只能接受现实
But now, I don't know. I'm dealing.
这么说你对死亡也无所谓了吗
So you're okay with dying?
当然不是
No, of course not.
我只是在想 该来的总是要来
I just think, whatever's gonna happen is gonna happen.
那不是我能够控制的
It's out of my control.
那就是命运
It's just fate.
也对 但这都是废话
Now, that's crap.
人总有选择的
You always have a choice.
你要么随即死去 要么无论发生什么都继续抗争
Roll over and die or keep fighting.
克莉斯蒂医生请到237室紧急抢救
Dr. Kripke to Room 237. Code blue. Dr. Kripke...
- 迪恩 你去哪里 - 你呆在那里等我
- Dean Where you going? - Just wait here.
开始装袋 准备出发
Start bagging. Ready to go.
再注射一针强心剂
Give me another amp of epi, please.
离她远点
Get away from her.
行了 结束了
Come on. Negative.
- 没有脉搏 - 好了 让我们宣布吧
- Still nothing. - All right. Let's call it.
死亡时间 下午5点11分
Time of death, 5:11 p.m.
至少她不用再受苦了
At least she's not suffering anymore.
嘿
Hey.
我想你可能就在这附近 如果你在
I think maybe you're around. And if you are...
不许笑话我 但是…
you'll make fun of me for this.
但有一种方式我们可以交流
But there's one way we can talk.
你不是拿这个逗我吧
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
迪恩
Dean?
迪恩 你在吗
Dean, are you here?
上帝 我觉得就像在睡衣派对
God, I feel like I'm at a slumber party.
好吧 萨姆
All right, Sam.
我估计这不会有用的
This isn't gonna work.
我真不敢相信
I'll be damned.
有你在真好 没有你一切都不对劲了
Oh, it's good to hear from you, man. It hasn't been the same without you.
迪恩
Damn straight.
这倒是实话
All right, all right.
迪恩 怎么了
Dean, what?
"H"... H...
"U"...U...
猎捕
"Hunt"?
还是猎鬼
What, hunting or?
你在猎鬼吗
Are you hunting?
迪恩 这是医院 你在猎捕什么
Dean, it's in the hospital, what you're hunting.
你知道你要猎捕的是什么吗
Do you know what it is?
伙计 拜托一次问一个问题
One question at a time, dude.
那是什么
What is it?
我不认为它在杀人
I don't think it's killing people.
它似乎只是要带走他们…
I think it's taking them.
你应该知道的 就是在…
You know, when...
当人们接近死亡的时候
When their time is just up.
死神
A reaper?
迪恩…
Dean...
它是不是要带你走
is it after you?
如果上天注定如此
If it's here naturally...
那是没有办法阻止它的
there's no way to stop it.
是啊 你不能杀了死神
Yeah, you can't kill death.
天啊 伙计…
Man, you're
我完了 萨姆
I'm screwed, Sam.
不可能
No. No, no, no.
一定有办法
There's gotta be a way.
一定会有的
Oh, there's gotta be a way.
爸爸肯定知道该怎么做
Dad will know what to do.
爸爸
Dad.
- 看来爸爸不在病房里 - 那他去哪里了
- Hey, so Dad wasn't in his room. - Where is he?
但我拿到了爸爸的日记 说不定里面会有解决问题的方法
But I got Dad's journal, so who knows? Maybe there's something in here.
谢谢你没有放弃救我 萨姆
Thanks for not giving up on me, Sammy.
该死的
Son of a bitch.
嗨 迪恩
Hi, Dean.
我刚读到了最有趣的内容
You know, you read the most interesting things.
比如 死神能够控制人的感觉
For example, did you know that reapers can alter human perception?
这我以前并不知道
I sure didn't.
简单来说 他们可以随心所欲地
Basically, they can make themselves appear however they want.
以不同的形式现身…
Like, say...
比如 一个美女
a pretty girl.
你显然比我上次 见到的那个死神要漂亮多了
You are prettier than the last reaper I met.
我一直在想你什么时候才能发觉
I was wondering when you'd figure it out.
我早该想到的
I should've known.
你那套所谓接受命运的说法
That whole "accepting fate" rap
对于一个将死之人来说 实在是冷静过了头
of yours is far too laid-back for a dead chick.
但是你母亲和那尸体 我还是不太明白那是怎么一回事
The mother and the body, I'm still trying to figure that out.
这是我的世界
It's my sandbox.
我可以让你看见 任何我想让你看见的东西
I can make you see whatever I want.
这算什么 这算是你的游戏吗 就为了玩弄我吗
What is this, like, a turn-on for you? Toying with me?
你没有我给我太多的选择余地
You didn't give me much choice.
如果你知道我的身份 你会发狂的
You saw my true form and you flipped out.
就象伤害了女孩子的感情一样
Kind of hurts a girl's feelings.
而这是唯一的方法能让我和你交谈
This was the only way I could get you to talk to me.
好吧
Okay, fine...
那我们谈谈 你究竟要和我谈什么
we're talking. The hell do you wanna talk about?
我想告诉你 死亡并不可怕
How death is nothing to fear.
是到时候该走了 迪恩
It's your time to go, Dean.
你活地已经比原先预定的要长了
You're living on borrowed time already.
[咒语]
伙计 你在这下面干什么
What are you doing down here?
- 让我解释下可以吗 - 可以
- I can explain. - Yeah?
去向保安解释吧
You're gonna explain to Security.
来吧 跟我走
Come on, you follow me.
嘿
Hey.
你把我当成白痴吗
How stupid do you think I am?
想要听实话吗
You really want an honest answer to that?
是你在召唤我 约翰 这真是意外啊
You conjuring me, John. I'm surprised.
我很了解你
I took you for a lot of things...
但是我没想到你会 做出这样傻事来自寻死路
but suicidally reckless wasn't one of them.
我随时都能射死你
I could always shoot you.
但你也可能射偏
You could always miss.
而且你只有一次机会了 不是吗
And you only got one try, don't you?
你真的以为你能抓住我吗
Did you really think you could trap me?
我并不想抓你
Oh, I don't wanna trap you.
我要和你做个交易
I wanna make a deal.
迪恩 你在这吗
Dean, are you here?
我在日记里找不到信息
I couldn't find anything in the book.
我不知道怎么才能帮你
I don't know how to help you.
但我一定不会放弃
But I'll keep trying, all right?
只要你能坚持下去 好吗
As long as you keep fighting.
我是说 你不能…
I mean, come on, you can't
你不能留下我一个人在爸爸身边
You can't leave me alone with Dad.
你很清楚我们两个会闹翻的
We'll kill each other. You know that.
迪恩 你必须坚持下去
Dean, you gotta hold on.
你不能放弃 绝不能现在放弃
You can't go, man. Not now.
我们好不容易才走到一起
We were just starting to be brothers again.
你听到了吗
Can you hear me?
我知道你以前听过这些话
Look, I'm sure you've heard this before.
但是… 你总得破个例什么的 再给我一次机会
But you gotta make an exception. You gotta cut me a break.
第三阶段 讨价还价
Stage 3, bargaining.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我的家人处于危难之中
My family's in danger.
我们正身陷…
See, we're kind of in the middle of this...
斗争之中
war.
我的家人他们需要我
And they need me.
战斗结束了
The fight's over.
- 不 还没有 - 但对你来说结束了
- No, it isn't. - It is for you.
迪恩… 你并不是我从战场上带走的第一个战士
Dean, you're not the first soldier I've plucked from the field.
其他人也都这么认为
They all feel the same.
觉得他们不能离开那里
They can't leave.
胜负未分
Victory hangs in the balance.
但是他们错了
But they're wrong.
没有他们 战斗依然还在继续
The battle goes on without them.
没有我 我弟弟会活不下去的
My brother. He could die without me.
也许会
Maybe he will.
但也许不会
Maybe he won't.
但你 都无法改变什么
Nothing you can do about it.
这样战死
It's an honorable death.
对于战士来说是光荣的
A warrior's death.
我想要是我遇到第72个处女 我还是会放弃的
I think I'll pass on the 72 virgins, thanks.
我对故作正经的女人向来没兴趣
I'm not that into prude chicks, anyway.
说得好
That's funny.
你真有趣
You're very cute.
世上根本没有光荣的死去这回事
There's no such thing as an honorable death.
我的尸体将会在地下腐烂 而我的家人也会因此而死去
My corpse is gonna rot in the ground. My family is gonna die.
不行
No.
我不会跟你走的 不管你怎么做
I'm not going with you. I don't care what you do.
那好吧 就像你说的…
Well, like you said...
总是有其他选择的
there's always a choice.
即使我不能带走你
I can't make you come with me...
但你也不可能回到你自己身体了
but you're not getting back in your body.
这是无法改变事实
And that's just facts.
所以你可以留下
So, yes, you can stay.
你能在这里游荡
You'll stay here for years...
但你没有实体 充满恐惧
disembodied, scared.
多年后你可能就会被逼疯的
And over the decades, it'll probably drive you mad.
你甚至会变得狂暴
Maybe you'll even get violent.
你这是什么意思
What are you saying?
迪恩
Dean...
你知道那些暴戾的灵魂 是怎么诞生的吗
how do you think angry spirits are born?
它们不肯离开但也不愿前进
They can't let go, and they can't move on.
而你正在变成它们中的一员
And you're about to become one.
变成那些你曾经猎杀的对象
The same thing you hunt.
和魔鬼做交易
It's very unseemly.
可不是一件好事
Making deals with devils.
我怎么知道这不是另一个计谋
How do I know this isn't just another trick?
这次肯定不是
It's no trick.
我会把柯尔特和那颗子弹给你
I will give you the Colt and the bullet...
但你必须帮助迪恩
but you gotta help Dean.
你必须把他带回来
You gotta bring him back.
为什么这样做 约翰 你还真是感情用事啊
Why, John, you're a sentimentalist.
真希望你的儿子们 能知道你是那么爱他们
If only your boys knew how much their daddy loved them.
这个交易不错吧
It's a good trade.
比起迪恩你肯定更想要这把枪
You care a hell of a lot more about this gun...
别这么快下结论
than you do Dean. Don't be so sure.
他杀了对我很重要的人
He killed some people very special to me.
不过 你是说的没错的 他的威胁并不大
But still, you're right. He isn't much of a threat.
当然你的另一个儿子也一样
And neither is your other son, of course.
你知道真相的 对吧
You know the truth, right?
关于萨姆
About Sammy...
和其他孩子
and the other children?
是的
Yeah.
我早就知道了
I've known for a while.
但是萨姆并不知道吧
But Sam doesn't, does he?
你一直瞒着他
You've been playing dumb.
你能把迪恩带回来吗
Can you bring Dean back?
能还是不能
Yes or no?
不能
No.
但我知道谁可以做到
But I know someone who can.
那并不成问题
It's not a problem.
很好
Good.
在我把枪给你之前
And before I give you the gun...
我必须亲眼 确定迪恩没事才行
I'm gonna wanna make sure that Dean's okay, with my own eyes.
约翰 我真是失望 难道你不信任我吗
Oh, John, I'm offended. Don't you trust me?
那好吧
Fine.
这么说成交了
So we have a deal.
没有 约翰 还没有
No, John, not yet.
你还得加大筹码
You still need to sweeten the pot.
你还想要什么
With what?
还有一些东西是我想要的
There's something else...
就像那把枪一样
I want as much as that gun.
可能比枪更重要
Maybe more.
是时候把痛苦放下了
It's time to put the pain behind you.
放下后去哪里呢
And go where?
对不起
Sorry.
我不习惯拐弯抹角
I can't give away the big punch line.
是做出最后的选择的时刻了
Moment of truth.
以后没有机会改变决定了
No changing your mind later.
你的决定是什么呢
So, what's it going to be?
你这是在干什么
What are you doing that for?
这不是我干的
I'm not doing it.
到底是什么…
What the hell?
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
滚开
Get away!
发生什么事了
What's happening?
今天是你的幸运日 小子
Today's your lucky day, kid.
迪恩
Dean.
医生 我需要帮助
Help! I need help!
我无法解释这些
I can't explain it.
水肿现象消失了 内伤也好了
The edema's vanished, the internal contusions are healed.
你的情况看上去一切良好
Your vitals are good.
可能天使正保护着你吧
You've got some kind of angel watching over you.
谢谢你 医生
Thanks, doc.
- 你说有个死神要带走我吗 - 是的
- You said a reaper was after me? - Yeah.
- 那我怎么摆脱他的呢 - 因为你有我
- How'd I ditch it? - You got me.
迪恩 你真的什么都不记得了吗
Dean, you really don't remember anything?
不记得了
No.
除了胃有点难受之外
Except this pit in my stomach.
萨姆 有些不对劲
Sam, something's wrong.
伙计 你感觉怎么样
How you feeling, dude?
我想还不错
Fine, I guess.
- 我还活着 - 那就好
- I'm alive. - That's what matters.
你昨晚在哪里
Where were you last night?
我有些事情要办
I had some things to take care of.
哦 那还真是巧啊
Well, that's specific.
够了 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
你是不是去追那恶魔了
Did you go after the demon?
- 没有 - 你也看得出我不会相信你的话
- No. - Why don't I believe you right now?
我们可以不争吵吗
Can we not fight?
我们一直都在争斗 我甚至都不明白我们在争些什么
Half the time I don't know what we're fighting about.
我们这样只能自乱阵脚
We're just butting heads.
听着 萨姆
Sammy, I've
我犯了一些错误
I've made some mistakes.
但我都尽量做到最好
?But I've always done the best I could.
我只是不想再争吵了 好吗
I just don't wanna fight anymore, okay?
爸爸 你还好吗
Dad, are you all right?
我没事
Yeah.
只是有点累而已
I'm just a little tired.
嘿 孩子 能帮我…
Hey, Sam, would you mind...?
能帮我带杯咖啡来吗
Do you mind getting me a cup of caffeine?
好的 没问题
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
你想说什么
What is it?
你该了解的 当你还是孩子时
You know, when you were a kid...
每次我猎鬼归来
I'd come home from a hunt.
目睹了那一切以后
And after what I'd seen...
我几乎都快崩溃了
I'd be wrecked.
而你
And you...
会走到我面前
You'd come up to me...
把手放到我的肩膀上 看着我的眼睛
you'd put your hand on my shoulder, and you'd look me in the eye.
然后对我说 一切都会好的 爸爸
You'd say, "It's okay, Dad."
迪恩
Dean.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为什么要对我说抱歉
Why?
你不必这样问我 而我也该早点对你说这些话
You shouldn't have to say that to me. I should've been saying that to you.
我…
You know, I put
我让你背负的太多 我让你过早的挑起重担
I put too much on your shoulders. I made you grow up too fast.
你不仅照顾萨姆 而且还要照顾我
You took care of Sam, and you took care of me.
你的确做到了
You did that.
而你从来都没有抱怨过 一次都没有
And you didn't complain, not once.
我只是想让你知道
I just want you to know...
我因此为你感到自豪
that I am so proud of you.
- 这就是你想说的吗 - 是的
- This really you talking? - Yeah.
是的 没错
Yeah, it's really me.
你为什么要说这些
Why are you saying this stuff?
我要你看着萨姆 好吗
I want you to watch out for Sammy, okay?
当然可以 爸爸 我一定会的
Yeah, Dad, you know I will.
你差点吓到我了
You're scaring me.
别害怕 迪恩
Don't be scared, Dean.
好了 他已经回来了
Okay.
爸爸
Dad.
- 你必须在外面等 - 不要 这是我们的爸爸
- You'll have to wait outside. - No, it's our dad.
五百毫升的准备
Five hundred cc's ready to go.
- 好吧 让我们再试一次 再来一支阿托品 - 振作…
- Let's try again. An amp of atropine. - Come on.
推动阿托品
Pushing atropine.
在推
In.
好了 不能再压了
Okay, stop compression.
停止
Stopped.
最后的呼吸
Last breath.
- 伙计 醒过来啊 - 仍然没有心跳
- Come on, come on. - Still no pulse.
好了 各位 结束了 我来宣布吧
Okay, that's it, everybody. I'll call it.
确定死亡时间 上午10:41
Time of death, 10:41 a.m.